President, Office of the; Records ua000
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Office of John M. Sayles, 1930-1950; 3; 4.67
  - Admissions, 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Adult Education Council, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Albany Home for Children, 1944-1947 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - American Council on Education, 1945-1947 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - American Council on Education, 1942-1945 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of NY Committee on Teacher Education - Speight, Harold, Executive Secretary, 1939-1943 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Association of Colleges and Universities of the State of NY - Five Year Plan Teacher Education, 1940; Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - American Association of Teacher Colleges, 1939-1946 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - American Association of University Women, 1940-1947 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - American Council on Education, 1940-1942 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - American Committee for Democracy and Intellectual Freedom, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1939-1946 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Annual Report, 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Annual Report, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Annual Report - Milne Report, 1945-1946 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Annual Report - Placement Bureau, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Annual Report - Placement Bureau, 1947-1948 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Association of Colleges and Universitites of the State of NY - Albany Faculty Workshop, 1940-1942 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Association of Secondary School Principals, 1938; 1945; 1946 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - American Association of Teacher Colleges, 1940-1944 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Associated Academic Principals of NYS, 1939-1941 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - NYS Association of Faculties of Teacher Colleges and Normal Schools, 1939-1940 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - NY Association of Teachers College Faculties, 1944-1946 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Athletics, 1932 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Audio - Visual Aids, 1944-1945 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Aviation Workshops Study Conference on Education for the Air Age, 1942-1946 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - B - Correspondence, 1939-1946 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Baccalaureate Sunday, 1940-1946 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Board of Regents (Organization Charts), 1940-1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Office of the President Board of Vistors, 1939-1948 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Brubacher Student Memorial Brubacher Bio, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Budget Matters, employee information, 1942-1948 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Budget, NYSCT, 1939-1944 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - [Teacher] Appointment Bureau, 1942-1947 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1939-1946 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Centennial Celebration, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Chemistry Department - Remodeling, 1941-1943 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Chemistry Laboratory, 1942-1946 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Civil Service Annual Rating, 1947-1948; 1950 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Commencement, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Commeres Department, 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Committees - Report, 1941-1947 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Conference on Teacher Education, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Conference of Administrators, 1940-1941 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Cooper, Herman, 1939-1943 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Cooper, Herman (Assistant Commissioner for Teacher Evaluation, 1939-1946 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Cooper - Property, 1939-1944 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Cooperative Test Service B.W Wood, 1939-1941 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Council on Cooperative in Teacher Education, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Curriculum, 1937-1945 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Department of Civil Service, 1944-1947 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1938-1944 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Departmental Reports Milne High School, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Departmental Reports Dean's Office, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - E - Correspondence, 1940; 1944 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Dormitory Authority - Correspondence + Minutes + By Laws, 1944-1947 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - English Department Report, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Education Policies Commission, 1939-1941 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Executive Dean for Education, Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Executive Dean for Teacher Education (SUNY), 1942-1947 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - F - Correspondence, 1939-1946 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Faculty - Administration Council (Faculty Council), 1944-1952 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Appointments and Changes, 1939-1945 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Federal Aid, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Federal Housing, 1946; 1948 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Financial Reports - Losses, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Fisk Roberts, 1946; 1948 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Office of the President Five Year Plan, 1939; 1946; 1947 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - French House, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Freshman Addresses Classes 1941-1940, 1941 September-1946 September (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Fraternities and Sororities, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - William M. French, 1942-1946 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - G - Correspondence, 1939-1946 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - James Gemmil, 1942-1948 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Gideon Hawley & Milne Murals, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Graduate School - AU Departments, 1935-1945 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - H - Correspondence, 1941-1947 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Hardy, Wm G., 1941-1947 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Hastings, Harry, 1941-1945 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Hatfield, D. Elliot, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Hickey, Dorothy, Undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Home Economics Department, 1943-1944 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Housing Information, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Hutchins, Ruth Art Department WPA, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - I - Correspondence, 1942-1947 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Individual Reports from Various Departments for Annual Reports, 1944-1945 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Institute of International Education, 1942-1947 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Institutution of Pacific Relations, 1946 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Interculture Relations, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Interculture Relations, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Intergroup Relations, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - J - Correspondence, 1939-1946 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - K - Correspondence, 1933-1947 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - L - Correspondence, 1941-1947 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Lang, Varley Military, 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Leaves of Absences, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Legation of Switzerland, Letter, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - NYS Legislature, 1941-1946 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Letters from Almuni, etc (Centenial Celebration), 1944 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Library Committee - Report, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Library School, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - M - Correspondence, 1934-1947 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Mathematics Department, 1941-1944 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Memoranda File, 1929-1947 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Hillis Miller - Association Commissioner of Higher Education, 1945-1947 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Middle Statue Association, 1941-1946 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Military Training, 1941-1943 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Milne High School, 1939-1946 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Montgomery Ward Scholorship, 1935-1936 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - N - Correspondence, 1939-1946 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Student Peronnel Committee - Elizabeth Morris - Educational Testing, 1934-1946 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - National Teacher Examinations, 1940-1941 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - New York State War Council (War Training Programs), 1942 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - New York Times "Test" on American History, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - National Camp - Life Camps, 1942-1945 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Milton G. Nelson - Dean, 1942-1947 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - National Education Association, 1939-1947 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - National Youth Administration, 1941-1942 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - U.S Navy, 1942-1947 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Need for a State University, 1947-1948 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - New York State Teacher's Association, 1941-1942 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - New York State Teacher's Association, 1943-1947 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - NYSCT - Misc, 1931-1947 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Clippings, ca. 1940 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - O - Correspondence, 1941-1945 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - P - Correspomdence, 1940-1947 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Placement Date, 1941-1943 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Plans for Downtown Campus, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Personal Notes of 1944 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Post War Education (Floor Plans and Room Space for Future Development), 1944 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Post War Education Facilities, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - President's Annual Report of the New York State College for Teachers, 1939-1940 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Physical Education, 1941-1947 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Placement Date, 1943-1949 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Police Department, 1943-1949 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - President's Annual Report of the New York State College for Teachers, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - President's Annual Report of the New York State College for Teachers, 1941-1942 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - President's Annual Report of the New York State College for Teachers, 1942-1943 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - President's Report, 1938-1941 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - President's Report, 1941-1944 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - President's Annual Report of the New York State College for Teachers, 1943-1944 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - President's Annual Report of the New York State College for Teachers, 1944-1945 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - President's Annual Report of the New York State College for Teachers, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Projection of the Five Year Plan for the Improvement of the Teacher's College, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Questionnaire, 1942-1947 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Religious Education, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Reports: American Association of Teacher's College, Undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Report of Department of Education, 1945-1946 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Report of Examination of Income Accounts and Financial Records, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Report of the Projected Five Year Plan, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Residence Halls, NYSCT, 1940-1941 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - S - Correspondence, 1936-1947 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Sabol, Edward Correspondence, 1944-1946 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Schmidt, AW (Assistant Commission of Finance), 1936; 1940-1949 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Schmidt, AW, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Science and Geography Department, Undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Service Flag Dedication, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Signum Laudis, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Smith, Dr Dormal V, 1942-1942; 1947-1948 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Special Fund Estimate, 1945-1947 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Stewart, Watt, Correspondence, 1945-1947 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - St. Mary's Park Veterans Housing, Dormitory, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Student Christian Association, 1939-1942 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Student Injuries During Class Rivalry, 1940 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Student Union, 1945-1949 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Summer Sessions, 1940-1947 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Survery of Critical Materials (Divisions of Standards and Purchase), 1942 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Syracuse Conference "Competence of Teacher Coverage Students", 1947 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - T - Correspondence, 1942-1947 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Teacher's College, 1940-1945 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Teacher - Placement - NYSCT Albany, 1949-1950; 1958 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Teacher Training, 1939-1940 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - U - Correspondence, 1941-1946 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - United States Office of Education, 1941-1946 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - U.S Army, 1943 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - University Club, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - V - Correspondence, 1941-1947 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - W - Correspondence, Undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - War Man Power Commission, 1943-1944 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - War Relief Control Board, War Finance Committee, 1943 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - War Service Oppurtunity, 1942-1943 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Katherine Wheeling Retirement, 1946-1947 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Walter Woodward - Correspondence Re Milne High School, 1945 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Workshop, 1941 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - George York - NYSCT Commerce Department, Undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Office of Milton Nelson Records, 1946-1951; 4; 0.80
  Series is arranged in alphabetical order.
  The materials in this series cover this over two year period that Nelson was in the position of President of the college. Milton G. Nelson was acting President in the wake of John Sayles sudden illness in the winter of 1947. The materials include reports from the president, correspondence with faculty and staff, as well as some select materials from Nelsons time as Dean of the College.
  - American Association of Colleges for Teacher Education, 1947-1949 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 1)
  - American Council on Education, 1947-1948 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 2)
  - Baccalaureate Sunday, 1947-1948 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 3)
  - Board of Visitors, 1947-1948 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 4)
  - Budget, 1948-1949 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 2)
  - Budget Director's Approval, 1948 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 5)
  - Campus student Teaching, 1947-1948 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 6)
  - Commencement Programs Correspondence, 1947-1949 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 7)
  - Committee Appointments, 1947-1949 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 3)
  - Construction, Improvements, 1947-1948 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1947 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 9)
  - Coorespondence W, 1947 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 10)
  - Curriculum and Graduate committee, 1948 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 11)
  - Department of Education report, 1947-1948 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 12)
  - Department Reports, 1947-1949 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 13)
  - Executive Dean for Teachers Education, 1947-1949 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 14)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1947-1949 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 15)
  - Faculty Status, 1951 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 16)
  - Federal Security Agency, National Youth Administration, 1939 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 17)
  - Freshman Addresses, 1952 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 18)
  - Gemmel, Professor James, 1948 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 19)
  - Heyden, Velma, 1948 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 20)
  - Housing (Dormitories and Cafeteria), 1946-1950 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 21)
  - Housing (Dormitories and Cafeteria), 1946-1950 (Box 1 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 22)
  - Housing (Dormitories and Cafeteria), 1946-1950 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 1)
  - Huyck Preserve, 1945 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 2)
  - Inter-Group Council, 1947 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 3)
  - Invoices, H, 1948-1949 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 4)
  - Invoices, I, 1948-1949 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 5)
  - Invoices, L, 1947-1949 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 6)
  - Men's Athletic Association Manual, 1948-1949 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 7)
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1947-1949 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 8)
  - Misc. J-K Invoices, 1948-1949 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 9)
  - Physical Education Report, 1947-1948 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 10)
  - Rhodes, Scholarship Trust, 1947 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 11)
  - Sabol, Edward Correspondence, 1947-1949 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 12)
  - State Architect, 1947 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 13)
  - St. Mary's Park- Emergency Veterans Housing Reports, 1947-1949 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 14)
  - Student Medical Insurance, 1947-1948 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 15)
  - Student Union, 1947-1949 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 16)
  - Survey of Fiscal Affairs for the State College, 1949 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 17)
  - Teacher Placement Brueau, 1948 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 18)
  - Vaccines, 1947 (Box 2 (4-Office of Milton Nelson Records), Folder 19)
- Office of Evan R. Collins Records, 1949-1969; 5; 14.92
  Conditions Governing Access
  This file series is semi-processed and may contain some records that must be withheld due to public records laws. Please consult an archivist for more information.
  This series contains materials related to the presidency of Evan Revere Collins, who held the position from 1949-1969. The origin of these materials trace to both Evan Collins himself, as well as the Presidential office from this time. These cover the important changes occurring on the campus at this time, including expansion of the downtown dormitories at Alumni Quadrangle, as well as the construction of the Uptown Campus, and the change of the New York State College for Teachers, into a University Center. Specific materials in the series include reports from individual departments, correspondence with staff and contractors, and annual reports form Collins, as well as those sent to the office of the president such as the Milne School annual report. There are some materials that date to after Collins presidency, and were most likely part of the records keeping of the Office of the President after the move to the uptown campus.
  - Contents
- Faculty File, 1928-1957; 6; 2.31
  Series is arranged in alphabetical order by surname.
  This series is made up of faculty files kept for members of the staff of the New York State College for Teachers. There is a file dedicated to each individual faculty member, containing hiring information, correspondence, and in some instances grades and transcripts sent in as part of an application.
  - Contents
- Personal Records of Allan A. Kuusisto, 1967-1970; 7; 0.4
  Materials include University plans and reports related to protests, as well as personal records of Kuusisto such as his Curriculum Vitae.
  - Budget 1970-1971, 1969 (Box 1 (7-Personal Records of Allan A. Kuusisto), Folder 1)
  - Curriculum Vitae, 1969 (Box 1 (7-Personal Records of Allan A. Kuusisto), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1967-1970 (Box 1 (7-Personal Records of Allan A. Kuusisto), Folder 3)
  - President's Administrative Reorganization Plan, 1968-1969 (Box 1 (7-Personal Records of Allan A. Kuusisto), Folder 4)
  - Student Disorder Viet Nam Protests, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (7-Personal Records of Allan A. Kuusisto), Folder 5)
  - Wagner, Gerard, faculty arrest, student protests, 1970 (Box 1 (7-Personal Records of Allan A. Kuusisto), Folder 6)
- Personal Records of Louis T. Benezet, 1969-1974; 8; 0.4
  Materials in the series consist of budget reports, memos and plans of administrative events, and correspondence to individual faculty as well as the University as a whole.
  - Allen Center, 1972 (Box 1 (8-Personal Records of Louis T. Benezet ), Folder 1)
  - Alumni Fund, 1973 (Box 1 (8-Personal Records of Louis T. Benezet ), Folder 2)
  - Budget, 1973-1974 (Box 1 (8-Personal Records of Louis T. Benezet ), Folder 3)
  - Budget Reports, 1970-1974 (Box 1 (8-Personal Records of Louis T. Benezet ), Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box 1 (8-Personal Records of Louis T. Benezet ), Folder 5)
  - CUPA College and University, 1972-1974 (Box 1 (8-Personal Records of Louis T. Benezet ), Folder 6)
  - Publications; Academic Leadership: Of What or Of Whom?, 1972-1974 (Box 1 (8-Personal Records of Louis T. Benezet ), Folder 7)
  - Social Studies Center, 1972 (Box 1 (8-Personal Records of Louis T. Benezet ), Folder 8)
  - SUNY Atmospheric Sciences Research Center, 1970-1972 (Box 1 (8-Personal Records of Louis T. Benezet ), Folder 9)
  - SUNYA Economic Impact Study, 1970 (Box 1 (8-Personal Records of Louis T. Benezet ), Folder 10)
  - SUNYA Sciences, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (8-Personal Records of Louis T. Benezet ), Folder 11)
  - SUNYA Mathematics Department, 1969-1974 (Box 1 (8-Personal Records of Louis T. Benezet ), Folder 12)
  - State University Professional Association, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (8-Personal Records of Louis T. Benezet ), Folder 13)
- Personal Records of Emmett B. Fields, 1975-1977; 9; 0.2
  Series includes information on budegts and Fields' departure from the University.
  - Budget, 1977 (Box 1 (9-Personal Records of Emmett B. Fields ), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 1 (9-Personal Records of Emmett B. Fields ), Folder 2)
- Records of the Office of the President, 1948-1977; 10; 50
  Series is arranged in the original order.
  This series is made up solely of materials kept in the Office of the President. While the items date from 1948-1977, the majority of the materials date from after the construction of the uptown campus, with many pieces dating from the presidency of Louis Benezet. The subject of the materials vary greatly, and cover important events in the University history such as the construction and relocation to the uptown campus and campus unrest in 1970. The president covered in this series are Nelson, Collins, Kuusisto, Benezet, and Fields. Many boxes contain papers related to multiple presidents, connected by a common subject at times. Others are dedicated to a single president and subject. Specific materials in the series include blueprints of new construction, annual reports, master plans for the University, and reports from individual departments.
- Personal Records of Vincent O'Leary, 1977-1981; 11; 0.2
  Materials are made up of correspondence, budget reports, and O'Leary's Curriculum Vitae.
  - Budget, 1978-1981 (Box 1 (11-Personal Records of Vincent O'Leary), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1977-1986 (Box 1 (11-Personal Records of Vincent O'Leary), Folder 2)
  - Curriculum Vitae, 1977 (Box 1 (11-Personal Records of Vincent O'Leary), Folder 3)
  - Health Law, Human Subject for Research, 1977 (Box 1 (11-Personal Records of Vincent O'Leary), Folder 4)
- Office of Vincent O'Leary Records, 1960-1990; 12; 118
  Maintained in the original order as transferred from the Office of the President
  Administrative Records from the term of Vincent O'Leary (1977-1990)
  - Contents
- Office of H. Patrick Swygert Records, 1977-1998; 13; 100
  Administrative Records from the term of H. Patrick Swygert (1990-1995)
  - Contents
- Office of Karen R. Hitchcock Records, 1995-2004; 14; 112
  Administrative Records from the term of Karen R. Hitchcock (1995-2004)
  - Contents (incomplete listing)
- Records of the Office of the President, 2004-2009; 15; 25
  Administrative records during the tenure of John R. Ryan, (2004-2005), Kermit L. Hall (2005-2006), Susan Herbst (2006-2007), George M. Philip (2007-2009), and Robert J. Jones (2013-2016).
  - Contents
- Website of the Office of the President, 2013 May 2 - 2017 July 17; 16; 83 Captures
  URL
  http://www.albany.edu/administration/office-of-the-president.php
  Access Requirements
  The item contains web archives preserved as WARC files. They must be access though web archival replay tools such as the "Wayback Machine." The links here direct you to files hosted by the Internet Archive, but you may also request WARC files.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Web crawling is managed through the Internet Archive's Archive-It service.
  This item is not a seed within an Archive-it collection, but capures of this page are found within:
  collection: University at Albany, SUNY Website
  created_date: 2012-09-17T13:15:00Z
  created_by: bkeough
  state: ACTIVE
  last_updated_date: 2016-09-26T23:38:05Z
  last_updated_by: system
  Web Collection
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2013 May 2